[BILLY] In a way,
I should actually thank you.
If you hadn't stolen LoveFeast,
I wouldn't have thought
of something much better.
Which one of us is the bigger thief?
Why don't you just tell the truth,
so I can understand
where your anger is coming from?
Your relationship with Caloy?
- We don't have a relationship.
- [JORDAN] You don't?
Hi, dude. Good morning!
Auntie Pres's birthday is coming up.
What's our plan?
Let's see.
I'll get going.
I've got things to do.
[BILLY] Kris? Hi!
Oh, you're near?
Okay, I can meet you outside.
Yes. See you in a bit.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
- Hi, Kris!
- Hi, Billy.
- Nice to finally meet you.
- Likewise.
[BILLY] What are you doing there?
I'm just taking a break.
Okay. Um…
Jordan, I want you to meet
Kristina Salintado.
She's an influencer.
- Jordan.
- Kris.
You're Kris.
Yes, Kris.
- Yes, nice to meet you.
- I thought…
Never mind.
Thank you so much.
- Kris.
- Kris, yes.
- She's Kris.
- Yeah.
I don't know if it's right
to feel this way about Sir Eric.
[LYDIA] Then try Sir Eric too.
Just tell him how you feel.
[PRECIOUS] Oh, please. I don't even know
if what I'm feeling for Eric is right.
[LYDIA] Are you a teenager? Are you?
Are you still going to play hard to get?
Olive. Do I really have to stay away
from our children now?
I want to apologize to Billy,
but I don't want to make things
harder for her.
You can tell me anything.
Is it about your family?
If you're not ready to talk, that's fine.
Just know that I'm here for you, Sir Eric.
Just call me Eric.
Mm.
Okay. I'm here for you, Eric.
[ENRICO] Thanks for…
keeping me company.
[PRECIOUS] Don't mention it.
I just want to repay your kindness.
Dude. You know what
Auntie Pres would like?
- Hmm?
- Filipino food.
- That's her favorite.
- Correct.
It should be a Filipino restaurant.
I know the perfect place.
Auntie Pres is going to love it, I know.
Let me see. Oh, you're not sick anymore.
You're so happy and full of energy now.
- Huh?
- Good mood today, huh?
I wonder why.
You like her, don't you?
Kris?
- Mm.
- No.
Then why did you go downstairs earlier?
You even went to greet her.
And you keep repeating her name.
- Mm? Mm? Mm?
- Dude! It's not like that.
- You got it all wrong.
- Oh, really?
- Me?
- Yeah.
- Fine, you don't like her.
- I thought…
You like me.
- Huh?
- Me.
Whatever.
You're too gullible.
Come on. Back to work.
Wow!
You're up early, Ms. Supervisor.
Are you leaving already?
Well, I have to.
I have a lot of work to do as supervisor.
Ah…
Well, if your sister were here,
she'd be proud of you.
You're successful, just like her.
- Hmm? Do your best, dear.
- [CHUCKLES]
I will, like I always do.
[MARIELA] All right, take care!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Mm?
Why don't you look excited
about your leadership camp?
Oliver…
It's overnight, okay?
So don't forget your patch.
You're going with your classmates.
But it's on the same day
as Auntie's birthday.
You don't have to go if you don't want to.
But you'll have to write
a reflection paper instead.
But I really want to go, Billy.
I'm a student leader.
If I don't attend,
I might not get elected
student leader again next school year.
Oh, so that's what this is about.
But I don't want to miss
Auntie's birthday either.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Auntie will understand.
We can always do a video call.
Then, we'll celebrate again
when you get back.
I know!
I'll just do a video call with her.
And… what would be
an awesome gift for Auntie?
Do you know what's the best birthday gift
you can give to Auntie?
Good grades.
That's the best gift
you can give Auntie Pres.
And to me too.
Okay, Billy. I'll do my best
at the student leadership camp!
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you sure you want to go?
Yes! Sign it, please.
It has no ink.
All right, I'm signing it now.
- Thank you, Billy!
- One day without this rascal!
My goodness!
- Are you going to miss me?
- A bit.
- Just a bit?
- Don't forget your patch, okay?
- You'll miss me just a bit?
- And your medicine.
If there's a problem, call me immediately.
Your teachers already know. Okay?
- You promise.
- Yes, I promise. I promise.
- Be good, okay?
- Yes.
- You'll miss me, right?
- Mm-hmm.
You promise?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGING]
Pres.
Do you have any plans later?
[PRECIOUS] Why?
There's something I want to tell you.
[PRECIOUS] Huh? About what?
I want to tell you in person.
Can we meet?
Hmm… Okay. Sure.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGING]
[SQUEALING] Lydia!
I think he's planning to confess to me!
Yeah.
I didn't expect things would go this fast
after knowing each other
for only a few weeks.
[PRECIOUS] Yeah, Lydia.
All right, all right.
I'm done second-guessing!
I'm taking the risk!
[SQUEALS]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Dude, I already called the restaurant.
They want to know the headcount.
Who are you inviting?
Probably the staff from Angels of Grace
and Auntie Pres's friends.
Okay.
So how are we setting this up?
I'll figure something out, dude.
But you're in charge
of the entertainment, okay?
[CHUCKLES] Leave it to me.
Anything for you.
Okay. Thank you.
- [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Auntie Pres is here.
- [PRECIOUS] Billy?
- I'll hang up now. Bye.
Yes, Auntie?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- Wow!
- Hm?
Wow!
- [CHUCKLES]
- You look beautiful!
Thank you.
Are you going somewhere?
Just going out to get some fresh air.
Nice.
Would you like me to get you a scarf?
- Yes. It may be too windy.
- Yeah.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Let me see…
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, this would look good
on you, Auntie Pres.
- Yes.
- Oh!
- Sorry, Auntie Pres!
- Don't use that.
- Why?
- Wipe it off.
- I forgot to throw it away.
- What's wrong with it?
This is from Mariela.
- Ugh! My goodness, Billy!
- Yeah.
[BILLY LAUGHS] Sorry.
Why'd you keep it?
I forgot to throw it away. I'm sorry.
Use this one instead. It's safe.
- Should I wash--?
- No, it's okay.
- What?
- You're good.
- My goodness.
- Here.
That's the right decision, Enrico.
You need to tell your children's
mother figure the truth about who you are.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I wouldn't really call Precious
a mother figure.
They see her as their real mother.
Oh.
All the more reason
why you should come clean.
It'll help lighten the burden
you're carrying.
Even if there's a chance
she'll get angry with me
and I won't get to see my children again?
What's important is that you're honest
with the person who loves them.
And with the woman you love.
You love Precious, don't you?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
How was work, dear?
Mm!
Exhausting, Ma.
I had so much to deal with.
There were so many screw-ups!
[LAUGHING]
My daughter really is amazing.
Come on, eat.
- I know you're hungry.
- Yes, Ma.
I cooked sinigang.
[WOMAN 1] Sorry, Ms. Mercado,
but we can't process your application
without a police clearance.
[WOMAN 2] Miss, you have a pending case?
[WOMAN 3] We can't hire you, Ms. Mercado.
Your involvement with Carlos Toledo
is all over social media.
We don't accept applicants
with connections or ties to criminals.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Good evening, Chief.
Can you check these records?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's all clear. Get him inside.
- Yes, sir. Thank you.
- Go ahead.
Let's go.
- Thank you, Chief.
- Take care on your way home.
Take good care of him.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SHUTTERS CLICKING]
[MAN 1] Oh, fresh fish!
- Come on!
- Chief, put him here!
All of you, get some sleep.
[METAL DOOR CREAKS]
- [MAN 1] Chief, put him here!
- Hey, quiet down!
Get some sleep.
[MAN 2] Can we have him here?
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [MAN 3] I'll take care of you later.
[MAN 4] What?
[CHUCKLING]
Go ahead. Go to your bed.
[TALIA] What are you doing here?
I thought you were in jail.
What? I've done nothing wrong!
You were working together with that thief!
No! That's not true!
- Whoever said that--
- Security, take her outside!
- Ms. Talia, I just need a job!
- Now, go!
- I'm begging you, Ms. Talia! Please!
- [GUARD] Please leave, ma'am.
- [BEA] Ms. Talia!
- Billy?
Bea's here and she's making a scene.
I thought our plan would put her in jail.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC SLOWLY FADES]
- Oh.
- Mm!
Looks like you've had quite a few.
Not really.
Have you ordered? What do you want?
Oh, nothing. I'm fine.
I'll just have whatever you're having.
I'm sorry for bothering you. Just…
There's something I wanted
to tell you face-to-face.
What is it?
Precious, these past few weeks,
I've grown closer to you.
- Mmm?
- Uh…
I've seen what a kind person you are.
Um…
I've seen how much you love the children…
- Your children.
- Mm-hmm.
And I realized that
you need to know the truth.
Precious,
there's something I need to confess.
I'm torn.
I don't know if I should tell you.
I'm afraid you'll get angry.
I won't get angry.
What is it you want to tell me?
[VOICE BREAKING] Precious…
I'm sorry.
But the truth is…
I love you too.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Are we good? Okay?
Okay.
Uh…
Waiter? Uh…
One… one beer for her, please.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
["TRAFFIC" PLAYING]
♪ It's such a waste of time
Being stuck in traffic ♪
♪ It's so damn frustrating ♪
♪ What if this never happens again? ♪
♪ My body aches from sitting for hours ♪
♪ I'm starting to hesitate ♪
♪ What if you suddenly go home? ♪
♪ Baby, I'm sorry, I'm still dreaming ♪
♪ I can't blame this on anyone ♪
♪ If only I could fly over EDSA ♪
♪ Then I wouldn't have to wait ♪
♪ Why is it like that? ♪
♪ So many are rushing to get ahead ♪
Hey!
♪ Why does it feel so far
When you're right there? ♪
♪ I'm afraid I won't catch up
If the world stops ♪
♪ I'm willing to try
Even if I get stuck in traffic ♪
♪ What number am I in line? ♪
- ♪ Maybe I can get ahead ♪
- [BILLY CLAPS]
♪ I promise I won't back down ♪
♪ From your suitor ♪
♪ Baby, I'm sorry, I'm still dreaming ♪
♪ I can't blame this on anyone ♪
♪ If only I could fly over EDSA ♪
- ♪ Then I wouldn't have to wait ♪
- [GIRLS SHRIEK]
♪ Why is it like that? ♪
♪ So many are rushing to get ahead ♪
♪ Why does it feel so far
When you're right there? ♪
♪ I'm afraid I won't catch up
If the world stops ♪
♪ I'm willing to try ♪
♪ Even if I get stuck in traffic ♪
♪ Everyone ♪
Hey!
♪ Is trying to get ahead ♪
♪ Why does it feel so far
When you're right there? ♪
♪ I'm afraid I won't catch up
If the world stops ♪
♪ I'm willing to try ♪
♪ Even if I get stuck in traffic ♪
- [CROWD CHEERING]
- [JORDAN] Thank you!
[MUSIC FADES]
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CROWD CHEERING]
Contact party giveaway supplier.
Confirm orders of flowers
for the centerpiece, okay.
Centerpiece, okay.
Follow up catering
and cake supplier.
Hmm. What should we use?
The function room or the main dining room?
We should do it in the function room.
It's more private there.
Okay.
And let's finalize the menu.
It's going to be tomorrow.
Wait, wait. I want you
to listen to this. Wait.
I think this suits Auntie Pres.
["ABELYANA" BY MAKI PLAYING]
- It's perfect.
- Mm!
- I'm good with that.
- Right?
Nice, right?
- It's great. Perfect.
- Mm-hmm.
You know what, dude?
I didn't expect Auntie Pres
to find love again…
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
…after Uncle Rico died
right on their wedding day.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BILLY] Even if it's uncertain,
many still take risks on love.
Because once it happens,
it'll completely change a person's life.
This can't be.
I don't think anyone
remembered my birthday.
Can I take you out
to dinner later?
It'll be great.
It'll be just the two of us.
Do you know
who Auntie Pres is dating?
Hasn't she told you?
It's Sir Eric.
Your aunt is dating Sir Eric.
- Cute.
- Hmm.
Why didn't Auntie Pres tell us
that she was dating Sir Eric?
Maybe she's still shy about it.
Well, if they're really dating,
I hope we can meet him.
- Surprise!
[PRECIOUS CHUCKLING]
Billy!
You even made a fool of the person
who raised us and cared for us
when that should have been you?!